<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Eevee: Reunited - Character Demo</name>
    <directory>eevee_reunited_demo</directory>
    <id>2653691445</id>
    <description>[img]https://imgur.com/nvTka55.png[/img]

(Be sure to uninstall the old AB+ Eevee! There will obviously be compatibility issues)

Eevee: Reunited is an overhaul project of the original [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1809450880]Eevee Mod for Afterbirth+[/url]. This aims to reunite every Eeveelution back to Eevee as the original mod always meant to do, all with unique attacks, many unique Pokémon-themed items, and much more. This is a demo release that only contains Eevee, for the purpose of gaining support for the project and putting forward the quality you can expect for the full release. If you would like to follow development or directly contribute to the mod, join the Discord Server linked below. We're looking for spriters and artists, but coders are also welcome. Enjoy the mod!

[h1][url=https://discord.gg/A8ffZkg8b8]Join the Discord![/url][/h1]
[h1][url=https://twitter.com/EeveeMod]Follow constant updates on the Dev Twitter![/url][/h1]

[img]https://imgur.com/4LN8j07.png[/img]
Everything you can expect from downloading the mod.
[list]
[*]1 new character: Eevee - Fight through with your charge-up move, Swift!
[*]While firing, summon orbiting stars around you. Once 5 stars are summoned or you let go of firing, they will be unleashed forth and home in on enemies! Note: This attack can miss.
[*]40+ item synergies! Most of your favorite attack-changing items and unique effects for certain items.
[*]Unique costume support! Eevee has 500+ unique costumes, and any costumes that would otherwise harm Eevee are automatically removed on the spot!
[*]Birthright: Tail Whip! With this secondary move, keep your distance by knocking back any harm that comes your way, and lowering the defense of enemies.
[/list]

[img]https://imgur.com/7WtTfi8.png[/img]
Eevee is compatible with a handful of mods. If you want to see Eevee compatible with certain mods, feel free to suggest them!
[list]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1590327567]NO COSTUMES[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2519706865]Custom Co-Op Ghosts[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2376005362]Encyclopedia[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=836319872]External Item Descriptions[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2615720951]Mega Mush CostumeSuffix Compat[/url] -Required for custom Mega Mush costume
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2487535818]Mod Config Menu[/url] -Allows you to toggle a custom Mr. Dolly sprite based on stewartisme's [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2489635144]Custom Mr. Dollys[/url] (Default: Off) and a unique Spirit Sword (Default: On).
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2490515687]POG for Good Items[/url]
[/list]

[img]https://imgur.com/h0807Zb.png[/img]
When the mod is done, it’ll be made into a separate upload so people can enjoy either the big mod pack, or the simplicity of pure Eevee. “Eevee: Reunited” will feature:
[list]
[*]All 8(+?) Eeveelutions, only able to be obtained in a run through Eevee, each with their own unique attacks, costumes, and birthrights.
[*]Tainted Eevee, who’s gimmick surrounds mix-matching Eeveelution abilities
[*]Collectibles, pickups, and trinkets tied to character unlocks for Eevee and Tainted Eevee, all based on various Pokémon items.
[*]Secrets???
[/list]

[img]https://imgur.com/fgaODN0.png[/img]
[u]On The Team[/u]
Sanio – Lead Dev. Creator of the OG Eevee Mod, made all code and sprites not mentioned otherwise.
Fertifo0 – Artist. Art on most of the Steam Workshop images, excluding ones already mentioned below.
Stewartisme – Spriter. Made various costume sprites, Mega Mush sprite, and Giant Cell Eevee familiar sprites.
Eevee's boss/stage portrait was made between all 3 of us.

[u]Artists[/u]
CheapBones – Eevee: Reunited logo
TikaraTheMew – Workshop Thumbnail Art
SGTX – Doodles in Workshop description titles.

[u]Other[/u]
Ilias – Assisted in Eevee’s sprite redesign
Seb135, lambchop_is_ok, fly_6, ChemicatGamingYT – Playtesters
Special thanks to JSG, Agent Cucco, siraxtas, wofsauge, Sentinel, Im_tem, everyone above and many others for their continued support!
You - Checked out this workshop page! You're cool! Thank you!</description>
    <version>1.10</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Sound Effects"/>
</metadata>
