<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Eevee: Reunited - Character Demo</name>
    <directory>eevee_reunited_demo</directory>
    <id>2653691445</id>
    <description>The current plan for the 'Demo' is to release large updates that feature key features of the full mod one at a time when they're completed, release small updates with feedback and bug fixes, then work on the next big update. The most recent one is the item unlocks. Next are Eeveelutions, and then ending at Tainted Eevee. A release date for the full version is set to November 21st, Eevee Day, where this demo will be marked as [OLD] and will give a message at the start of a run with Eevee saying to download the properly full version.

[img]https://imgur.com/nvTka55.png[/img]

[h1]PLEASE READ BELOW![/h1]

(Be sure to uninstall the old AB+ Eevee! There will obviously be compatibility issues)

Eevee: Reunited is an overhaul project of the original [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1809450880]Eevee Mod for Afterbirth+[/url]. This aims to reunite every Eeveelution back to Eevee as the original mod always meant to do, all with unique attacks, many unique Pokémon-themed items, and much more. This is a demo release that will slowly gain updates over time for the purpose of gaining support for the project, receiving feedback, and putting forward the quality you can expect for the full release. If you would like to follow development or directly contribute to the mod, join the Discord Server linked below. We're looking for spriters and artists, but coders are also welcome. Enjoy the mod!

[h1][url=https://discord.gg/A8ffZkg8b8]Join the Discord![/url][/h1]
[h1][url=https://twitter.com/EeveeMod]Follow constant updates on the Dev Twitter![/url][/h1]

[img]https://imgur.com/4LN8j07.png[/img]
Everything you can expect from downloading the mod.
[list]
[*]1 new character: Eevee - Fight through with your charge-up move, Swift!
[*]While firing, summon orbiting stars around you. Once 5 stars are summoned or you let go of firing, they will be unleashed forth and home in on enemies! Note: This attack can miss.
[*]40+ item synergies! Most of your favorite attack-changing items and unique effects for certain items.
[*]Unique costume support! Eevee has 700+ unique costume sprites, and any costumes that would otherwise harm Eevee are automatically removed on the spot!
[*]Birthright: Tail Whip! With this secondary move, keep your distance by knocking back any harm that comes your way, and lowering the defense of enemies.
[*][b][NEW][/b] A full set of character unlocks and a new pickup type: Poke Ball!
[*][b][NEW][/b] A new challenge: 'Pokey Mans: Crystal'. Fight using only your Pokemon and defeat Mom!
[/list]

[img]https://imgur.com/7WtTfi8.png[/img]
Eevee is compatible with a handful of mods. If you want to see Eevee compatible with certain mods, feel free to suggest them!
[list]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1590327567]NO COSTUMES[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2519706865]Custom Co-Op Ghosts[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2376005362]Encyclopedia[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=836319872]External Item Descriptions[/url]
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2615720951]Mega Mush CostumeSuffix Compat[/url] -Required for custom Mega Mush costume
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2681875787]Mod Config Menu[/url] -Allows you to toggle a variety of options for your Eevee experience!
[*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2490515687]POG for Good Items[/url]
[/list]

[img]https://imgur.com/h0807Zb.png[/img]
When the mod is done, it’ll be made into a separate upload. The demo will slowly update over time with major content updates for the purpose of gaining feedback, with the full release being the final push for quality and polish. The full release will feature:
[list]
[*]All 8 Eeveelutions, only able to be obtained in a run through Eevee, each with their own unique attacks, costumes, and birthrights.
[*]Tainted Eevee, who’s gimmick surrounds mix-matching Eeveelution abilities
[*]Collectibles, pickups, and trinkets tied to character unlocks for Eevee and Tainted Eevee, all based on various Pokémon items.
[*]Secrets???
[/list]

[img]https://imgur.com/fgaODN0.png[/img]
[u]The Team[/u]
Everything in the mod was done by us unless stated otherwise below
[img]https://imgur.com/d6eihY6.png[/img]


[u]Artists[/u]
CheapBones – Eevee: Reunited logo
TikaraTheMew – Workshop Thumbnail Art
SGTX – Doodles in Workshop description titles.
Candle - Lil Eeveelution sprites
Jam - Boss/Stage portrait for Eevee

[u]Other[/u]
Ilias – Assisted in Eevee’s v1 sprite redesign (Before the unlocks update)
Kotry - Full Spanish translation for the mod's EID descriptions!
Seb135, lambchop_is_ok, fly_6, ChemicatGamingYT – Playtesters
Special thanks to JSG, Agent Cucco, siraxtas, wofsauge, Sentinel, Im_tem, everyone above and many others for their continued support!
You - Checked out this workshop page! You're cool! Thank you!</description>
    <version>1.19</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Trinkets"/>
    <tag id="Cards"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Challenges"/>
    <tag id="Sound Effects"/>
</metadata>
